Okay. It's really genetic, it sounds like
Well, I knew
Yeah. It's hard to say. It's yeah, it's
hard to say. But I mean I have six
children.
My youngest daughter was just like me. I
knew she was like me because she had an
eye
turn when she was three, like I did. And I
had taken her to the doctor and they put
her in glasses. It was just, you know, the
same process. And she was fine. She did
fine in school. She didn't seem to
struggle that much in other things. She
didn't
seem to be s super clumsy.
I had done other things with her when she
was very young, like music and movement. I
taught music and movement classes. And so
there were things that maybe compensated
better. I don't know. And I didn't see her
doing poorly in school or having any
struggles. And I had this passion for
sharing the whole thing, you know, because
I
knew it could help. I hadn't helped me
yet, but I knew it could.
And so I was reading this book called W if
when your ch Sorry When Your Child
Struggles by David Cook. And it had a
checklist in it of things to ask the
child.
And I was thinking about it in
relationship to c children that I was
experiencing at
school when I was substitute teaching. But
I practice I decided to practice the
questions on my daughter. And so I said I
said to her, Do the words ever do this
when you're reading?